# Contact 03341771779

aghani@students.uit.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/abdulmuheet-ghani-57a01a204 (LinkedIn)

https://github.com/Abdulmuheet-ghani/RV32I-Single-Cycle (Github)

#### Top Skills

Verilog

C/C++

Fusesoc

Assembly language

YAML

PLC

## Abdul Muheet Ghani

Karachi Division

#### Summary

Abdul Muheet Ghani is a third year student of Electrical Engineering (B.E) at UIT Karachi, working on MERL (microelectronic research lab)

Pursuing my Bachelor's Degree in Electrical (Electronics)
Engineering, from Usman Institute of Technology-UIT-NED. Along
with core technical skills related to my field, I have attained few
creative skills like RISC-V single cycle core and multistage pipelining
In Verilog and System Verilog and also run compliance test on
My single cycle and further Implemented a wishbone bus protocole.

Learning new innovating skills which are essential for my career boosting, i am always open to them.

Soft Skills:

Agility, Strategic Thinking, Drive, Critical Analyst and thinker, Challenging Nature, Innovation, Presentation Skills, Analytical Skills, Communication Skills.

#### Open For:

Seeking better opportunities to make a successful career in focus RISCV processor designing and verification field this emerging field.

### Experience

Mindstorm Engineering Internship Trainee August 2021 - Present (4 months) karachi

ZIMCO International Corporation Intern July 2021 - Present (5 months) karachi

Automation Play Ambassador May 2021 - Present (7 months) Karāchi, Sindh, Pakistan

Micro Electronics Research Lab Research Internee January 2022 - Present (2 months) karachi

### Education

Usman Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Journalism · (2005 - 2012)